Guide to the Ingram Olkin papers SC1221
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers
  - Math 259B - Lecture, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sampling - W. Madow, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Set theory and metric spaces - E. H. Spanier, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Topological Algebra/Rings of Operators I. Kaplansky, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Letters to Olkin, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - On Convergence of Convex Minorant Algorithms for Distribution Estimation Under Censored Data, 1991 Aug. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Existence and Uniqueness of the Maximum Likelihood Estimator for the Two-Parameter Negative Binomial Distribution, 1991 Aug. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Repeated Measurement Arma-Processes II, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - An Error Components Model Applied to Almost Ideal Demands for Transportation, 1992 June (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Models for Estimating for the Fail-Safe Number in the File Drawer Problem, 1991 Oct. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Simulations of Iterative Procedures for Maximum Likelihood Estimation in MA(1) Models, 1994 July (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Best Nonnegative Invariant S-Orthogonal Quadratic Estimation in Normal Regression, 1992 June (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Numerical Procedures for Estimating the Parameters in a Multivariate Homogeneous Correlation Model with Unequal Variances, 1993 Dec. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Some Inequalities for Symmetric Convex Sets with Applications, 1993 Sept. 27 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - A Sequential Decision Problem Involving Several Agents, 1994 July (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correlations Redux, 1994 Aug. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Multivariate Exponential and Geometric Distributions with limited Geometry, 1994 Sept. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Multivariate Non-Normal Distributions and Models of Dependency, 1994 March (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Correlation Analysis of Extreme Observations from a Multivariate Normal Distribution, 1994 April (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Pattern Identification of Arma Models, 1994 July (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Inference for Autocorrelations under Weak Assumptions, 1993 Aug. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Multivariate Assessment of Computer Analyzed Topographs, 1992 July (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Numerical Aspects in Estimating the Parameters of a Mixture of Normal Distributions, 1992 Sept. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Stochastically Dependent Effect Sizes, 1992 Sept. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Monounsaturated Versus Polyunsaturated Dietary Fat and Serum Lipids: A Meta-Analysis, 1994 July (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Letters to and from Olkin, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Jes Correspondence, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Jes Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Jes Correspondence, 1980-1988 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Jes Management Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Jes Budget, Editor, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Letters to and from Olkin, 1985-1990 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Report of the External Review Panel for the Department of Statistics, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Letters to and from Olkin, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - NSF Proposals, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Letters to and from Olkin, 1984-1988 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - NSF Proposal Multi-Dimensional Statistical Analyses, 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - NSF Proposal - I. Olkin, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - NSF Proposal Multi-Dimensional Statistical Analysis, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - NSF #DMS 85-08383 Final Report "Cross Disciplinary Research"..., 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - NSF Proposal Current, 1983 Nov. 15 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - NSF Oversight Committee, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - NSA Renewal Models and Structures of Mult. Dist., 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Letters to and from Olkin, 1982-1986 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Comments and Recommendations on Aro Research Proposal, 1982 Oct. 22 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Proposal Evaluation Form, 1984 Jan. 13 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - 1995 COPSS Awards Presentation and Fisher Lecture (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Proposal No. 93G-133, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - NSF Proposal, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Robust Statistical Interface: Weighted Likelihoods or Usual M-Estimation?, 1996 Dec. (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Estimation of Effect Sizes with Multiple Treatments and a Common Control, 1995 Feb. (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Goodness-of-Fit Tests for Probability Distributions and Spectral Distributions, 1995 March (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Wavelets and Time-Dependent Spectral Analysis, 1995 April (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - The Decomposition of the Behrens-Fisher Statistic in Q-Dimensional Common Principal Component Submodels, 1995 Dec. (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Minimal Conditions for Weak Convergence of the Sample Spectral Distribution Function, 1995 May (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - New Families of Life Distributions with Extreme Stability, 1994 Dec. (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Meta-Analysis and its Applications in Horticultural Science, 1995 Jan. (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - When Does a*A = B*B and Why Does One Want to Know?, 1995 Feb. (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - A Stochastic Em Estimator in the Presence of Missing Data - Theory and Applications, 1994 Nov. (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - A Stochastic Em Algorithm for Approximating the Maximum Likelihood Estimate, 1994 Sept. (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Estimation in Second Order Dependency Model for Multivariate Binary Data, 1994 Oct. (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - A Stochastic Difference Equation Approach to Inference with missing Data: Some New Results, 1994 Oct. (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Weighted Likelihood Equations with Bootstrap Root Search, 1996 Dec. (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Correlation Analysis of Ordered Observations from a Block-Equicorrelated Multivariate Normal Distribution, 1996 Nov. (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - A Comparison of Effect Estimates from Meta-Analysis of Published Data and Effect Estimates from Pooled Patient Data, 1996 Sept. (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Two-Stage Sampling for Inference of the Difference of Two Multivariate Normal Means, 1996 Aug. (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Ruin Problems with Assets and Liabilities of Diffusion Type, 1996 July (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Efficiency of Adaptive Sampling Designs for Spatially Clustered Populations, 1996 July (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Comparison of Meta-Analysis Versus Analysis of Variance of Individual Patient Data, 1996 June (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Models for Estimating the Number of Unpublished Studies, 1995 Sept. (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Quantitative Synthesis of Independent Studies, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Multi-Dimensional Statistical Analysis, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - NSF Proposal for Research Project, Synthesis of Independent Studies/ 2 year period, 1981 Oct. - 1983 Sept. (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - NSF Grant DMS-8514938 Int'l Conf. on Found. of Statistical Inf., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - NSF Proposal - Multivariate Statistical Analysis, 1983 April-June (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Proposal: Int'l. Conf. on Foundations of Stat. Inference: Appli. in Medicine..., 1985 Dec. (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - NSF Support of Visitors' Program, 1982 Oct. 1- 1985 Sept. 30 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Draft of McClure Problem and Reply, 5-24-1984 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Guthrie, Donald, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Birman, Bea, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Promotion of Amemiya to Full Professor, 1-14-1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Query for University Position, 1975 Jan. - 1977 Jan. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Kraemer, Helena, 1978 June-July (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Contributions to the Theory of Sequential Analysis, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Alder-Roessler - Statistical Procedures, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Scheffe on Contrasts, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Mathematical Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Professor H. P. Starke Proof, 11-12-1956 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Review of MTAC, 5-20-1958 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Review of Sampling Theory of Surveys with Applications, 7-23-1957 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Some Aspects of Multivariate Analysis, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Evaluation of Research Proposal, 9-14-1959 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Basic Ordinance Research Program, 7-1-1958 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Statistical Documents, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Matrix Calculus Review, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - The Theory of Matrices Review, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Latest Structure, 9-2-1952 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Analysis of Experimental Models by Least Squares Review, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Outline of Probability Theory for Statistical Methods, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Journal Collection, 1958-1961 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - View Request for Air Force and Response, 1965 May (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Elashoff's Revision, 1965 Nov.-Dec. (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Elashoff's Paper Review, 2-23-1966 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - The Swazi Observer, 9-4-1982 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - The Times of Swaziland Vol.80 No.160, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - 1995 COPSS Awards Presentation and Fisher Lecture, 8-16-1995 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Airlie House Meeting on Applied and Theoretical Statistics, 1978 Feb. 9-11 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Best Linear Composites Review, 6-14-1966 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Measuring the Discrepancy Between Alternative Methods of Analysis, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Applied Mathematics Seminar, 1982 Nov. 8-12 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Committee on National Statistics - Mailing List, 9-1-1982 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - CNSTAT, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Overflow Letter, 1-24-1967 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - AAAS Fisher Papers, 7-19-1990 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous Letters to and from Olkin, 1967-1990 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Econometrics, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Bibliography - Multivariate Statistical Analysis, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Chapter 4: The Classical Model -- Some Practical Problems, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Chapter 5: The Classical Model -- Statistical Inference, undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Chapter 6: General Theory, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Chapter 7: Auto-Regression, undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Appendix A: Component Analysis, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Recommendations of Admissions Committee, 1985-86 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Quantitative Synthesis of Independent Studies, 1-23-85 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Chapter 3: The Classical Regression Model, undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Chapter 2: The Bivariate Normal Distribution and Correlation, undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Michael S. Garet, 1982 Nov. (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - MANOVA Example 2: Reading Data, undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Mulitivariate Analysis of Variance - Two Way Classification, undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Ottestad's Alternative to Component Analysis, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - David Rogosa, 1982 Nov. (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - MATH 541: Applied Multivariate Analyses, undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Range Restrictions For Product-Moment Correlations Matrices, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Biserial Correlations, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Multivariate Analysis, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence, 1976-82 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, 1987-92 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Correlations, undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Press, undated (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Student Notes, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Stat 324B Lecture Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Women in Mathematics, undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Women in Statistics - Ph.D's, undated (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Analysis of Variance, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Black Notebook of Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Letter Enfant Terrible, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Math Reviews, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Study of Mathematically Precocious Youth, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Spademan, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Cubberley Library, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - ARMY - NCR Advisory Committee / 25081 - MA / Odell, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Joint Summer Research Conference, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - BECHHOFER, Robert, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Joint Summer Research Conference, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Ayabe, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Hurd-Shell Merit Program Talk, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Special Papers Committee - IMS, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Conference Board of the Mathematical Sciences, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Mathematical Tables, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Comments on Research Proposal, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Compound Symmetry, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Mallows-Richter Paper, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Ecton-Olkin, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - USOE Proposal, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Eaton-Olkin Inequality, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - NSF Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - NSF Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Matrix Facts, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Marshal-Olkin Life Distributions from Polya's Urn..., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Tong-Olkin Positive Dependence of a Class..., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - National Research Council Notes, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Hedges-Olkin "Indices of Consistency of Mastery Class for Criterion-Ref.", 1990 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Guttman/Olkin A Bayesian approach to mixture models..., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Olkin/Searls Statistical Aspects of Intenational..., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Olkin/Rachev Distributions with Given Marginals..., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Gleser-Olkin Estimation of Effect Sizes with..., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Winter 1979 250C, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - 16-page Handout "250C" Duplicated winter 1979, Fall 1973 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Huh/Olkin "Asymptotic Aspects of Ridge Regress., 1984 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Psycho. Bulletin #0080886-273 MOdeling Multivariate Effect Sizes, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - CHINA - September 1984, 0 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Report of External Review Committee, undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Coladarci, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Stat 314 Winter '78 Classwork, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Fulbright, undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Book Binding, undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - David Report, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Brown, Lawrence D., 1981 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Cavalli-Sforza, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Chalmers, Thomas C., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - 10N Bibliography, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Missing OBS, 0 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Scaling, undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Dirichlet Integrals, undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Bechhofer Multiplication Model, undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Proschan Factorization of a P.D. Matrix, undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Material for ASQC Talk, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - General Linear Hypothesis - talk, 11/1/1968 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Norms & Cond NOS, undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Corr- Olkin, Siotani, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Olkin-Siotani, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Olkin-Siotani, undated (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - U of M, undated (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Stanford University, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - NSF proposal, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Short courses (see also Gibbins), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Derman Draft 1, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Rewrite of Derman Master Copy, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Larry V. Hedges, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Estimation of Probability Densities Belonging to Specificed Families, undated (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Ghrye and Olkin "Unbiased Estimation of Functionsof Probability Distributions", 1961 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Assorted papers, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Talk on Cheb/neg, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Amer Stat Association Milwaukee Multi Ratio Est, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - H. Walker seminar Columbia Fund Ident in Anova 2 way class [Missing OBS], 1948 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Klein's Seminar, Ann Arbor Mult tets with a priori info, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Bibliography for Matrices. Problems for Reading Course in Mces., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Reichenbach--report for CCNY course (a) 3-valued logic & quantum phys. (b) th prob, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Report of the Operations Committee of the Institute of Mathematical Stat. P. II, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - MAA Science Policy Committee, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Anderson-Olkin, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Olkin-250 Exam, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Management Committee, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Markov Chains Examples, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Char of Dsns., undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Aspects of Correlational Analysis, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Statistics 7, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Families of Multivariate Distribution, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Statistics 314 Notes, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Proposal for Research Project in Multivariate Models in Reliability Theory, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Reliability Testing and Estimation for Single and Multiple Environments, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Watch Colloq Jacob of Matrix Trfns, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Stat 314 Fall Quarter 1974 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Hungary, 0 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - NSF Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - The Main Inequality and some extensions notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - P.L. Hsu + Misc., undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Estimation - Stat. 572 II, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Lecture notes -- math and stat for soc scientists, 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Homework notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Stat or 314A, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Note on Jacobians - Biom, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Psuedo Transposition - Katz-Olkin, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Bush -- Manuscripts and Correspondence, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Banerjee - spring balance designs, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Sequential test using range, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - independence of forms - exposition, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Thm on convex functions, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Math & Stat - Soc. Sci., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - National Science Foundation, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Proposal (Budget Sheet Only), 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence and Notes, 1957-1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Final Examination Education 351A, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 10th Cont. Des. Exp. Washington, D.C., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1955-1962 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - NSF Contract GP-3837, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Marshall-Olkin Status Reports Multivariate Models in Reliability Theory, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - NSF Proposal, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - NSF Proposal for Research Project, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - An Inequality on the Probability Content of Parallelepipeds Based on Circular Symmetry, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Matrix Theory Notes, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Exams, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1992 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Annual Faculty Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Eaton, Morris L., 1983 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Conway, Dolores, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Stanford Course Evaluation EDUC60 spring, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Stanford Course Evaluation EDUC60 winter, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Stanford Course Evaluation STAT660 winter, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Stanford Course Evaluation STAT ANALY autumn, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Education 250B spring, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Social Science Course, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Rogosa, David, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1987 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Meeting of the Institute of Mathematical Statistics, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Norms and Condition Numbers, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Multivariate Chebyshev Type Inequalities, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - notes, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Multivariate Chebyshev Type Inequalities, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Enclosure Theorems for Eigenvalues and Probability Inequalities, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Game Theoretic Proof that Chebyshev Inequalities are Sharp, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Multivariate Ratio Estimation for Finite Populations, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Factor Analysis summer, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Notes and Correspondence, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Olkin-Pratt Correlations, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Calculus of Variations - Mackie, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Finite Differences - Koopman, undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Anal. Var. - Wolfowitz, undated (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Large Sample Theory - Chernoff Fall Quarter, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Stanford - NSF Mult., 1962 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Olkin-Press, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Conference Board of the Mathematical Sciences, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Theory of Numbers - A. Brauer, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Linear Programming and Theory of Games notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - ANOVA summer, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Partial Differential Equations - Koopman, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Notes on Jacobians, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Remarks on Idempotent Matrices, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - PhD - Gothberg, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - IMS Central Region, 1954, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Contract Correspondence Stanford, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Leave of Absence, Univ Chicago, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Negotiated Contract MSU, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Doctoral Dissertation Committee, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Contd - multi corr models, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Stanley Symp, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Handout for Washington Meeting mult chebyshev inequalities, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Non-parametric Multivariate, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Kallianpur measure theory lectures, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Current Manuscripts, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - An Inequality for a sum of forms, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Potency Ratio, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Cholesky Decompositions, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Linear Algebra and Multivariate Ananlysis, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - "Estimating the Potency Ratio for a Multivariate Normal Model", undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Range Restrictions for Product-Moment Correlation Matrices, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - ETS - Tom Quirk, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - A Derivation of the Wishart Distribution using the Polar Transfor., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - A Simulation Procedure for Roots of..., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Potential Qual Problems, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Ch. 1, Models with Patterned Parameters, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - A matrix theorem based on the independence of quadratic forms, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - "Range Restrictions for Product-Moment Correlation Matrices", undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - An exposition on the independence of quadratic..., undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Measuring Rate of Attrition, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Lecture Notes: Statistics 371 COMM. on STAT. U. of Chicago SPRING, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Notes and Correspondence, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - National Science Foundation: Renewal Proposal of Research Grant, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - University Correspondence, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Abstracts for Hungarian Workshop, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Hungarian Conference, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Hungary, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Faculty of Statistics Meetings, 1961-1963 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Derman, Cy -- Corres. re Gleser-Olkin book, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - correspondence, 1982-1990 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Least SQ. - Wolfowitz, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - National Science Foundation correspondence, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 29)